

Ilan Vysokovsky



052-8369711



ilanvys@gmail.com







SKILLS

Javascript, Node.js, React,

Python, Java, C, C++,

MongoDB, SQL, Git,

MERN Stack, OOP,

Test Automation.

LANGUAGES

- Hebrew Native
- English Professional

ABOUT ME

I've served in unit 9900 in the IDF, specializing mainly as a Full Stack Web Developer. I am organized, collaborative and creative. Truly fascinated by adapting ideas, shaping them, and turning them into reality. I am hardworking and self-taught, fueled by a passion to move forward.

EDUCATION

B.Sc, Computer Science 2021 – 2024

The Hebrew University of Jerusalem

Computer Software Technician 2016 – 2017

Ort Singalovksi

WORK EXPERIENCE

Automation Team Lead IDF Intelligence – Space Center 2020 – 2021

- Developed a large-scale testing infrastructure, including microservices, CI, web GUI and scripting.
- Pushed towards improving the entire development process, aimed at reducing manual QA in favor of automated QA.

Head of Satellite Tech Induction Course IDF Intelligence – Space Center 2020

- Served as a commander of 12 interns from different backgrounds.
- Planned the course, while improving its schedule, contents, logistics and many other aspects.
- Taught educational and professional lessons, discussed values, and instructed workshops, preparing the interns for service in the unit.

Full Stack Web Developer IDF Intelligence – Space Center 2017 – 2020

- Developed an operational web application for resource management and intelligence collection planning.
- Worked in cross-functional teams engaging in collaboration with multiple IDF corps.
- Developed microservices architecture replacing legacy systems, which resulted in tremendous reduction of time-tomarket features release.